(Stuart:)the longer I'm alone,
the more desperate I get.
(Amy:)Stuart, believe it or not,
I understand.
(Amy:)You know, before I met Sheldon,
(Amy:)I was alone
for a really long time.
(Amy:)I was so desperate
(Amy:)for people to like me,
when I met these guys,
(Amy:)it took everything in my power
to hide my insecurity.
(laughing):
Okay, we're all feeling it.
(Stuart:)Yes, I'll go out with you.
(Amy:)Suddenly, the rabbit thing
makes sense.
(Leonard:)I'm surprised you wanted to go
to a sports bar, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Look at this blister.
(Sheldon:)Like it or not,
we're athletes now.
(Sheldon:)Besides, a bar is
where I belong.
(Sheldon:)I'm having female problems.
(Leonard:)If you're cranky and retaining
water, I have a theory.
(Howard:)Sheldon, instead of focusing
on Amy dating other guys,
(Howard:)maybe you should start thinking
about dating another girl.